<faq>

<!-- This FAQ.xml file was reconstructed from http://faqtor.sourceforge.net/faq.html -->

<!-- 
Note that you can comment out portions of your FAQ.xml file by doing
something like this.
-->

<section name="About">
<question>
What is FAQtor?
</question>

<answer>

FAQtor is short for "Frequently Asked Questions generaTOR".

</answer>

<question>
What does FAQtor do?
</question>

<answer>

FAQtor is a python script that enables you to easily create and maintain a list
of questions and answers in a configurable format.

</answer>

<question>

Can you show me a webpage that uses FAQtor?

</question>

<answer>
The page you are viewing was generated by FAQtor
</answer>

<question>
Who developed FAQtor?
</question>

<answer>

<a href="http://www.phil-schwartz.com">Phil Schwartz</a>

<p>

Dan Nygren made a few additions to Phil's excellent work to allow pointing a
reader to a particular section of the FAQ (e.g.
http://www.example.com/FAQ.html#About ), set the date last updated
automatically, and support for Python 2.7 .

</p>

</answer>

<question>
Why didn't you feed back this changes to the original FAQtor?
</question>

<answer>

I did make an attempt, but was unable to successfully do so.  Hosting my changes
per the license on github seemed to be the right thing to do.

</answer>


</section>
<section name="Usage">

<question>
What do I need in order to use FAQtor?
</question>
<answer>

Python 2.7 (or greater) is required.

</answer>

<question>
How do I run FAQtor?
</question>
<answer>
<pre>
$ python faqtor.py yourfaq.xml [yourconfig.cfg]
</pre>

<p>
A makefile has been provided to allow this to be done easier and keep all the
FAQtor files in a FAQ subdirectory and move the generated FAQ.html to the main
directory.
</p>

<pre>
$ make
faqtor.py FAQ.xml FAQ.cfg
chmod u=rw,g=r,o=r FAQ.html
cp -p FAQ.html ..
</pre>

</answer>

<question>
What does the XML input file look like?
</question>
<answer>

The FAQtor FAQ was generated with this XML file.
See <a href="./FAQ.xml">FAQ.xml</a> in the FAQtor source distribution.

The XML input file can contain HTML so I often have preformatted text sections to show portions of screen dumps:
<pre>
prompt> mycommand | grep ':CA' | sed 's/+//' | sed 's/;//' | sed 's/^[ \t]*//;s/[ \t]*$//' | sort | uniq 
FRU-Part-Number:CA01022-0680 05D  /371-2227-04
FRU-Part-Number:CA01022-0690 10G  /371-2219-07
FRU-Part-Number:CA06620-D023 A0   /371-2215-01
FRU-Part-Number:CA06620-D342 B0   /371-2228-02
FRU-Part-Number:CA06620-D382 A0   /371-2239-01
</pre>

... horizontal rules
<hr />

<strong>
	
Items that need to be strongly pointed out

</strong>

<hr />

<em>

Emphasized areas of text.

</em>

<hr />

... or lists:
<ul>
	<li> Feature A </li>
	<li> Feature B </li>
	<li> Feature C </li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h3>
Headings
</h3>

<hr />

<h4>
Different Headings
</h4>

<hr />

I also like to include a source for my information at the end of an answer so a
reader knows where the information in the answer came from.

<p>
(Source: Dan Nygren)
</p>

</answer>

<question>
What does the config file look like?
</question>
<answer>

The FAQtor FAQ s also generated using the config file in the FAQtor source
distribution. This file is optional.  If not supplied, defaults are provided.
See the <a href="./FAQ.cfg">FAQ.cfg</a> file in the FAQtor source distribution.

</answer>

<question>
Why would I want to use a config file if it's optional?
</question>
<answer>

Although FAQtor will use defaults, it is recommended that you create a config
file to customize the layout of the FAQ.

</answer>

</section>
<section name="XML input file">

<question>
What is the structure of the XML input file in?
</question>
<answer>

Please refer to the <a href="./README.xml">README.xml</a> in the FAQtor source distribution

</answer>

<question>
How do I refer to answers (from other documents or from within the FAQ itself)?
</question>
<answer name="referring to answers">

In the XML input file, within each answer section that you wish to refer to you
must assign a name-value entity. Only answers that you wish to refer to require
this additional syntax, which looks like this:

<pre>
<a href="www.example.com/FAQ.html#referring to answers">Referring to Answers</a>
http://www.example.com/FAQ.html#referring to answers
file:///home/dnygren/FAQtor/FAQ.html#referring to answers
</pre>
<p>

Now, anywhere you wish to refer to it, you simply use the anchor with the name
you just created. This name can be anything as long as it adheres to HTML
syntax rules.

</p>

You can use the URL in the summary of questions at the top of the FAQ, however
this can result in pointing to the wrong question if you don't add questions
sequentially and then get the question numbers out of order.

<pre>
<a href="www.example.com/FAQ.html#3_1">Referring to Answers</a>
http://www.example.com/FAQ.html#3_1
file:///home/dnygren/SW/Git/FAQtor/FAQ.html#3_1
</pre>



</answer>

</section>
<section name="Configuration File (optional)">

<question>
What format is the configuration file in?
</question>

<answer>

The config file uses a standard Windows INI file format.  For more information
on the config file, please refer to README.cfg in the FAQtor source
distribution. 

</answer>

</section>
</faq>
