XML file format:
================

The XML input file is structured as follows:

1. An opening and closing <faq> and </faq> tag contains all of the faq data.
2. The faq contains one or more "sections" each with a required "name"
parameter.
3. Each section contains one or more questions.
4. Each of the questions contains exactly one answer.

The "faq" tag:
==============

<faq>
... everything else ...
</faq>


The "section" tag:
==================

<section name="a section">
...
</section>

The "question" tag:
===================

<question>What is this?</question>

The "answer" tag:
=================

<answer>This is an answer</answer>

New in v0.6: the following can be used to create named anchors so that you can
refer to this answer from other documents or from within the faq:

<answer name="any_valid_anchor_name">

This expanded syntax is optional and was added to accommodate linking to
answers from elsewhere.  For example:

<question>How do I use this new feature?</question>
<answer name="new_feature">
By adding a name="" attribute to the answer tag
</answer>

After running FAQtor incorporating the above into your XML input file you can
create links within to this answer from another page, say "related.html":

<h1>New features</h1>

You can now refer to the FAQ from another page.
Click <a href="faq.html#new_feature">here</a> to see how.



Putting it all together:
========================

<faq>
  <section name="General">
    <question>What is this?</question>
    <answer>This is the xml input file format</answer>

    <question>Is it really this easy?</question>
    <answer>Yes, the xml file is structured in a easy to create manner</answer>
  </section>
  <section name="More info">
    <question>Is there anything else I need to know?</question>
    <answer>Yes.
            There are some "gotchas" that will be discussed later.
    </answer>
  </section>
</faq>

Additional notes:
=================

Leading and trailing whitespace is ignored by FAQtor.  So each section,
question and answer that requires leading and/or trailing whitespace will need
to include the HTML non-breaking space entity, namely:  &nbsp;

eg.

&nbsp;&nbsp;This line has two leading spaces.

As of FAQtor v0.7 you can now include html markup directly within the XML
document.  Although not syntactically correct XML, FAQtor will convert the HTML
specific markup (namely the < and > brackets) to XML-compliant entities
(namely, &lt; and &gt;).  This functionality is provided as a convenience to
users because it can be quite tedious to manually replace the start and end tag
delimiters with entities.

eg.

<answer>This answer requires a <br> linebreak</answer>

The content of the previous <answer> XML tag will be converted by FAQtor to
this:

<answer>This answer requires a &lt;br&gt; linebreak</answer>

The previous result will then be passed the XML parser.
